Guide to the Yale University Library Subject Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject cards, circa 1860-1979; Accession 2006-A-001
  - Massachusetts--H to Mathematics (Box 406)
  - Mathematics (cont'd) to Mauritius--C (Box 407)
  - Mauritius--D to Medals--A (Box 408)
  - Medals--B to Medicine--F (Box 409)
  - Medicine--F (cont'd) to Mediterranean Region--D (Box 410)
  - Mediterranean Region--E to Mental illness-U (Box 411)
  - Mental illness in Washington County to Mersey River (Box 412)
  - Merseyside--E to Meteorological services--I (Box 413)
  - Meteorological stations to Mexican Americans--E (Box 414)
  - Mexican Americans--H to Mexico--F (Box 415)
  - Mexico--G to Mexico (City)--D (Box 416)
  - Mexico (City)--E to Middle Ages--H (Box 417)
  - Middle Ages--H (cont'd) to Midwives--U (Box 418)
  - Mie, Japan (Prefecture) to Military art and science--J (Box 419)
  - Military art and science--M to Mimes--F (Box 420)
  - Mimesis in literature to Mines and mineral resources (by locality)--B (Box 421)
  - Mines and mineral resources (by locality)--C to Minorities (by locality)--B (Box 422)
  - Minorities (by locality)--C to Missions (by locality)--C (Box 423)
  - Missions (by locality)--C (cont'd) to Moberly, Mo.--H (Box 424)
  - Mobile, Ala.--B to Mollusks (by locality)--Y (Box 425)
  - Mollusks, Effect of water pollution on--C to Money (Box 426)
  - Money (cont'd) to Money (by locality)--U (Box 427)
  - Money (by locality)--U (cont'd) to Montenegro--H (Box 428)
  - Montenegro--I to Mormons and Mormonism--B (Box 429)
  - Mormons and Mormonism--C to Motet (Box 430)
  - Mother and child to Moving picture plays--H (Box 431)
  - Moving-picture plays--H (cont'd) to Moving pictures and music (Box 432)
  - Moving-pictures and television to Municipal government (by locality)--Z (Box 433)
  - Municipal government by city manager to Music--A (Box 434)
  - Music--A (cont'd) to Music (by locality)--O (Box 435)
  - Music (by locality)--P to Muslims in Azarbaijan (Box 436)
  - Muslims--B to Mythology, Classical (Box 437)
  - Mythology, Classical (cont'd) to Names, Geographical--H (cont'd) (Box 438)
  - Names, Geographical--I to Naples--H (Box 439)
  - Naples--I to National characteristics, Japanese (Box 440)
  - National characteristics, Japanese (cont'd) to Nationalism (by locality)--A (Box 441)
  - Nationalism (by locality)--B to Natural history--O (Box 442)
  - Natural history--O (cont'd) to Natural law (Box 443)
  - Natural law--A to Navaho reservoir (Box 444)
  - Navaho Indians to Neighborhood government--U (Box 445)
  - Nejd, Arabia to Netherlands--F (Box 446)
  - Netherlands--F (cont'd) to New Bedford (Mass.)--L (Box 447)
  - New Bedford, Mass.--M to New Mexico--H (Box 448)
  - New Mexico--H (cont'd) to New York (State)--E (Box 449)
  - New York (State)--F to Newspapers (by country)--U (Box 450)
  - Newspapers in education to Nigerian drama--H (Box 451)
  - Nigerian drama (English) to Norris Dam (Box 452)
  - Norristown, Pa.--P to Northwest, Pacific--I (Box 453)
  - Northwest, Pacific--M to Novgorodskaia letopis (Box 454)
  - Novgorod, Russia (Province) to Numerical calculations (Box 455)
  - Numerical calculations--C to Nutrition--A (Box 456)
  - Nutrition--A to Oceanica--D (Box 457)
  - Oceanica--D (cont'd) to Oklahoma--D (Box 458)
  - Omu, Nigeria to Ontario Region (Calif.)--H (Box 459)
  - Ontogeny to Oral contraceptives (Box 460)
  - Oral contraceptives--A to Organizational behavior--S (Box 461)
  - Osaka--P to Ottawa Valley (Ont. And Quebec)--B (Box 462)
  - Ottawa University (Kan.)--H to Pacifists (Box 463)
  - Pacifists--B to Painting (by locality)--L (Box 464)
  - Painting (by locality)--M to Paintings--D (Box 465)
  - Paintings--E to Pakistan--Y (Box 466)
  - Pakistan literature--H to Paleontology--T (Box 467)
  - Paleontology--T (cont'd) to Pallavas (Box 468)
  - Pallavas--H to Paper--P (Box 469)
  - Paper--P (cont'd) to Parasitology (Box 470)
  - Parasitology--A to Parole (Box 471)
  - Parole--A to Pavis, Battle of, 1525 (Box 472)
  - Pavilions--I to Peasantry--O (Box 473)
  - Peasantry--P to Pennsylvania--N (Box 474)
  - Pennsylvania--O to Peronism (Box 475)
  - Peronism--A to Personnel service in education (Box 476)
  - Personnel service in education (cont'd) to Peru--P (Box 477)
  - Peru--P (cont'd) to Petroleum industry and trade (Box 478)
  - Petroleum industry and trade--B to Philadelphia--S (Box 479)
  - Philadelphia (Pa.)--T to Philologists--P (Box 480)
  - Philologists (by locality)--B to Philosophy--A (Box 481)
  - Philosophy--A (cont'd) to Philosophy, Ancient--A (Box 482)
  - Philosophy, Ancient--A (cont'd) to Philosophy, Medieval (Box 483)
  - Philosophy, Medieval (cont'd) to Photochemistry (Box 484)
  - Photochemistry--A to Physical education teachers--G (Box 485)
  - Physical fitness to Physics--C (Box 486)
  - Physics--C (cont'd) to Piemonte (Italy)--A (Box 487)
  - Piemonte (Italy)--B to Plankton--F (Box 488)
  - Plankton--G to Plasma (Ionized gases) (Box 489)
  - Plasma (Ionized gases)--A to Poetry--A (Box 490)
  - Poetry--A (cont'd) to Poets, Russian--19thc. (Box 491)
  - Poets, Russian--20thc. to Poland--H (Box 492)
  - Poland--H (cont'd) to Poles in the French Indies (Box 493)
  - Poles in Galicia to Polish literature--H (Box 494)
  - Polish literature--H (cont'd) to Political parties--C (Box 495)
  - Political parties--D to Political science (Box 496)
  - Political science (cont'd) to Political science--P (Box 497)
  - Political science--P (cont'd) to Pollen (Box 498)
  - Pollen (cont'd) to Poor laws--D (Box 499)
  - Population policy--U to Port Mellon, B.C. (Box 500)
  - Port Moller, Alaska to Portugal--H (Box 501)
  - Possession (law)--A to Postal service--D (Box 502)
  - Postal service--E to Poverty (Box 503)
  - Poverty (cont'd) to Preaching--D (Box 504)
  - Preaching--H (cont'd) to Press--E (Box 505)
  - Press--F to Prices--U (Box 506)
  - Prices--U (cont'd) to Printing--H (Box 507)
  - Printing--H (cont'd) to Prints--T (Box 508)
  - Prints--T (cont'd) to Problem of many bodies--A (Box 509)
  - Problem of many bodies--C to Proletariat (Box 510)
  - Proletariat--A to Proteolytic enzymes--C (Box 511)
  - Proteolytic enzymes--M to Providence--I (Box 512)
  - Providence--M to Psychoanalysis (Box 513)
  - Psychoanalysis (cont'd) to Psychology--E (Box 514)
  - Psychology--H to Psychology, Religious (Box 515)
  - Psychology, religious (cont'd) to Public health nursing--U (Box 516)
  - Public health personnel--I to Public utilities--C (Box 517)
  - Public utilities--E to Puerto Rican literature--A (Box 518)
  - Puerto Rican literature--A to Pycnogonida (Box 519)
  - Pycnogonida--A to Quebec (Province)--P (Box 520)
  - Quebec (Province)--P (cont'd) to Race in literature--A (Box 521)
  - Race problems to Radio waves--P (Box 522)
  - Radio waves--S to Railroads (by locality)--E (Box 523)
  - Railroads (by locality)--E (cont'd) to Rain and rainfall--S (Box 524)
  - Rain and rainfall--T to Reading--S (Box 525)
  - Reading (by locality)--B to Reclamation of land (by locality)--G (Box 526)
  - Reclamation of land (by locality)--H to Reference groups--A (Box 527)
  - Reference service (libraries) to Refugees, Political (by locality)--V (Box 528)
  - Refugee, Religious to Regionalism in literature--S (Box 529)
  - Registers of births, etc. to Religion--A (Box 530)
  - Religion--B to Religions (Box 531)
  - Religions (cont'd) to Renaissance--G (Box 532)
  - Renaissance--H to Research (by locality)--B (Box 533)
  - Research (by locality)--C to Revegetation--S (Box 534)
  - Revelation to Rhine Valley--A (Box 535)
  - Rhine Valley--B to Right and left (Political science)--A (Box 536)
  - Right and left (Political science)--B to Roads--G (Box 537)
  - Roads--H to Romance languages (Box 538)
  - Romance languages (cont'd) to Romanians in Transylvania--H (Box 539)
  - Romanians in Turkey to Rome--H (Box 540)
  - Rome--H (cont'd) to Rosicrucians (Box 541)
  - Rosicrucians--B to Rural-urban migration (by locality)--A (Box 542)
  - Rural-urban migration (by locality)--B to Russian language--P (Box 543)
  - Russian language--P (cont'd) to Russian literature (by period)--18thC. (Box 544)
  - Russian literature (by period)--19thC. to Russo-Finnish War, 1939-1940 (Box 545)
  - Russo-Finnish War, 1939-1940 (cont'd) to St. Galler Klosterplan--A (Box 546)
  - Saint George, Bermuda (City) to Salta, (Argentina Province)--S (Box 547)
  - Saltash, Eng. To Sanskrit drama--H (Box 548)
  - Sanskrit drama--T to Saskatchewan--H (Box 549)
  - Saskatchewan--I to Scandinavian languages--E (Box 550)
  - Scandinavian languages--G to School lands--V (Box 551)
  - School libraries to Science--B (Box 552)
  - Science--B (cont'd) to Science--P (cont'd) (Box 553)
  - Science--P (cont'd) to Science, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 554)
  - Science and civilization to Scotland--B (Box 555)
  - Scotland--C to Sculpture (by locality)--N (Box 556)
  - Sculpture (by locality)--O to Seafaring life (Box 557)
  - Seafaring life (cont'd) to Security, International (Box 558)
  - Security, International--A to Semimetals--C (Box 559)
  - Seminarians to Serbian imprints--E (Box 560)
  - Serbian literature to Service, Compulsory non-military--U (Box 561)
  - Service (Theology) to Sex in motion pictures--D (Box 562)
  - Sex in rabbinical literature--S to Sheng (Musical instrument)--M (Box 563)
  - Sheng-ssu, China to Ships--M (Box 564)
  - Ships--N to Short stories, English--T (Box 565)
  - Short stories, English--T (cont'd) to Siberia--P (Box 566)
  - Siberia--R to Silver mines and mining--Y (Box 567)
  - Silver ores to Sino-Japanese Conflict, 1937-1945--L (Box 568)
  - Sino-Japanese Conflict, 1937-1945--P to Slavery (by locality)--M (Box 569)
  - Slavery (by locality)--N to Slavic literature--A (Box 570)
  - Slavic literature--B to Slovenian language--C (Box 571)
  - Slovenian language--D to Social choice (Box 572)
  - Social choice--A to Social history--C (Box 573)
  - Social history--H to Social problems (Box 574)
  - Social problems (cont'd) to Social sciences (Box 575)
  - Social sciences (cont'd) to Social scientists (Box 576)
  - Social scientists--A to Social values (Box 577)
  - Social values (cont'd) to Socialism in Bosnia and Herzegovina (Box 578)
  - Socialism--B to Socialism and Islam (Box 579)
  - Socialism and Islam--A to Sociology (Box 580)
  - Sociology (cont'd) to Sociology, Buddhist--J (Box 581)
  - Sociology, Christian to Soils--I (Box 582)
  - Soils--J to Songs, Brazilian--H (Box 583)
  - Songs, Breton to South Africa--D (Box 584)
  - South Africa--E to South Africa in literature (Box 585)
  - South African drama (English)--B to Southern States--E (Box 586)
  - Southern States--E (cont'd) to Soviet Union--C (Box 587)
  - Soviet Union--C (cont'd) to Soviet Union--E (Box 588)
  - Soviet Union--E (cont'd) to Soviet Union--F (Box 589)
  - Soviet Union--F (cont'd) to Soviet Union--H (Box 590)
  - Soviet Union--H (cont'd) to Soviet Union--P (Box 591)
  - Soviet Union--P (cont'd) to Soviet Union--S (Box 592)
  - Soviet Union--S (cont'd) to Spain--C (Box 593)
  - Spain--C (cont'd) to Spain--H (Box 594)
  - Spain--H (cont'd) to Spanish-American newspapers--N (Box 595)
  - Spanish-American periodicals to Spanish language--V (Box 596)
  - Spanish language--V (cont'd) to Spectrophotometry (Box 597)
  - Spectrophotometry--A to Spleen--S (Box 598)
  - Spline theory to Stars (Box 599)
  - Stars--A to Statesman--B (Box 600)
  - Statesmen--C to Steam-boilers (Box 601)
  - Steam-boilers--C to Stocks (Box 602)
  - Stocks (cont'd) to Streight's Expedition, 1863 (Box 603)
  - Strela computer to Students (by locality)--S (Box 604)
  - Students (by locality)--T to Sudan--C (Box 605)
  - Sudan--D to Sulphapyridine (Box 606)
  - Sulphate waste liquor to Surfaces (Technology)--P (Box 607)
  - Surfaces, Algebraic to Sweden--F (Box 608)
  - Sweden--F (cont'd) to Switzerland (Box 609)
  - Switzerland--A to Synapses--C (Box 610)
  - Synaptomys to Taiping Rebellion, 1850-1864 (Box 611)
  - Taiping Rebellion, 1850-1864 to Tales (by locality)--B (Box 612)
  - Tales, Brazilian to Taosim (Box 613)
  - Taoism (cont'd) to Taxation (Box 614)
  - Taxation (cont'd) to Taxation, Exemption from--F (Box 615)
  - Taxation, Exemption from--G to Teaching (Box 616)
  - Teaching (cont'd) to Technology--D (Box 617)
  - Technology--D (cont'd) to Telegraph--H (Box 618)
  - Telegraph--L to Temples, Buddhist (Box 619)
  - Temples, Buddhist (cont'd) to Texas--E (Box 620)
  - Texas--E (cont'd) to Thailand--A (Box 621)
  - Thailand--B to Theater--M (Box 622)
  - Theater--M (cont'd) to Theater (by locality)--L (Box 623)
  - Theater (by locality)--L (cont'd) to Theology--B (Box 624)
  - Theology--B (cont'd) to Thermodynamics (Box 625)
  - Thermodynamics (cont'd) to Tigriña language--V (Box 626)
  - Tlaxcala (Mexico: State)--R to Tobruk, Battle of, 1941-1942 (Box 627)
  - Tobu Group to Totalitarianism (Box 628)
  - Totalitarianism--A to Trade-unions (by locality)--C (Box 629)
  - Trade-unions (by locality)--C (cont'd) to Trade-unions and communism--I (Box 630)
  - Trade-unions and communism--J to Translations (by locality)--B (Box 631)
  - Transportations (by locality)--C to Treaty of Paris (1783)--A (Box 632)
  - Treaty of Paris, 1803 to Tristar (Jet transport) (Box 633)
  - Tritheism--C to Tumbuka language--R (Box 634)
  - Tumbuka language--T to Turkey--S (Box 635)
  - Turkey in Asia to Tz'u--H (Box 636)
  - Tz'u--H (cont'd) to Ukrainian literature--H (Box 637)
  - Ukrainian literature--H (cont'd) to Underdeveloped areas--H (Box 638)
  - Underdeveloped areas--I to United Arab Republic--S (Box 639)
  - United Empire loyalists to United States--C (cont'd) (Box 640)
  - United States--C (cont'd) to United States--D (Box 641)
  - United States--D (cont'd) to United States--E (Box 642)
  - United States--E (cont'd) to United States--F (Box 643)
  - United States--F (cont'd) (Box 644)
  - United States--F (cont'd) (Box 645)
  - United States--F (cont'd) to United States--H (Box 646)
  - United States--H (cont'd) (Box 647)
  - United States--H (cont'd) (Box 648)
  - United States--H (cont'd) to United States--M (Box 649)
  - United States--M (cont'd) to United States--P (Box 650)
  - United States--P (cont'd) (Box 651)
  - United States--P (cont'd) to United States--R (Box 652)
  - United States--R (cont'd) to United States--S (Box 653)
  - United States--S (cont'd) to Universities and colleges (by locality)--H (Box 654)
  - Universities and colleges (by locality)--I to Urban policy--T (Box 655)
  - Urban policy--U to Uruguay in literature (Box 656)
  - Uruguayan drama to Van Cleve family (Box 657)
  - Vancouver, B.C. toVenezuela--H (Box 658)
  - Venezuela--H (cont'd) to Verona--H (Box 659)
  - Verona--I to Vietnam--H (Box 660)
  - Vietnam--H (cont'd) to Villages--I (Box 661)
  - Villages--I (cont'd) to Visingso, Sweden--H (Box 662)
  - Vision to Voivodina--S (Box 663)
  - Volapük to Voyages and travels--1951- (Box 664)
  - Voyages and travels--1951- to Waka (Box 665)
  - Waka (cont'd) to War, Maritime (International law) (Box 666)
  - War, Maritime (International law) (cont'd) to Waste lands--J (Box 667)
  - Waste lands--M to Water-supply--W (Box 668)
  - Weights and measures--C to Wellfleet (Mass.)--P (Box 669)
  - Wellington, Australia (New South Wales) to West Virginia--P (Box 670)
  - West Virginia--S to Wildlife conservation--B (Box 671)
  - Wildlife conservation--C to Witchcraft--N (Box 672)
  - Witchcraft--P to Women--E (Box 673)
  - Women--E (cont'd) to Women (by locality)--I (Box 674)
  - Women (by locality)--J to Women in library science--U (Box 675)
  - Women in library to Woodwork--P (Box 676)
  - Woodwork--T to World politics--20thc. (Box 677)
  - World politics--20thc. to World War, 1914-1918 (cont'd) (Box 678)
  - World War, 1914-1918 (cont'd) to World War, 1914-1918--F (Box 679)
  - World War, 1914-1918--F (cont'd) to World War, 1914-1918--R (Box 680)
  - World War, 1914-1918--R (cont'd) to World War, 1939-1945 (Box 681)
  - World War, 1939-1945 (cont'd) to World War, 1939-1945--C (cont'd) (Box 682)
  - World War, 1939-1945--C (cont'd) to World War, 1939-1945--P (Box 683)
  - World War, 1939-1945--P (cont'd) (Box 684)
  - World War, 1939-1945--P (cont'd) to World War, 1939-1945 (by locality)--A (Box 685)
  - World War, 1939-1945 (by locality)--A (cont'd) toWorld War, 1939-1945 (by locality)--M (Box 686)
  - World War, 1939-1945 (by locality)--N to Württemberg--H (Box 687)
  - Württemberg--I to Yodo River and valley (Box 688)
  - Yoga to Youth (by locality)--N (Box 689)
  - Youth (by locality)--N to Yukon River Valley (Yukon and Alaska)--D (Box 690)
  - Yukon River and valley--H to Zimbabwe--I (Box 691)
  - Zimbabwe--M to Zoology (by locality)--C (Box 692)
  - Zoology (by locality)--D to Zyrardów, Poland--T (Box 693)